<dashboard>
  <label>About this App</label>
  <description>The Google Timeline / Locations App</description>
<row>
<panel>
<title>Google Timeline and This App</title>
<html>
  <p><b><font size="6"><a href="https://www.google.com/maps/timeline">Google Timeline</a></font></b><br></br></p>
 
   <font size="4"><p><i><b>Google Timeline</b></i> uses Google Maps to help you find the places you've been and the routes you've traveled. 
     </p><br></br><p>
  This app is designed to take the exported JSON format from Timeline, and provide two methods for importing and viewing this export.
  </p>
  <p>  
    See this URL for more information from Google : <b>https://support.google.com/maps/</b>
     </p></font>
  <br></br> 
  <p><font size="6">About the Dashboards</font><br></br>
  <p><font size="4">
    This App contains two dashboards that demonstrate the core functionality of Splunk with Indexed Extractions and using standard parsing on JSON files. The indexed extractions dashboard utilizes the tstats command to demonstrate how Splunk can use 
    indexed fields in order to return results more quickly then standard search time extracted fields.
    </font></p>
  </p><br></br>
  <p><font size="6">App Configuration</font></p>
  <font size="4">
  <p>This app requires an index named <b>google</b> to exist and the data to be loaded into this index.
  </p>
  <br></br>
    <p><b>This app also requires the <a href="https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/3164/">Location Tracker Custom Visualization</a> is installed.</b></p>
    <br></br><p>
  There are two sourcetypes associated with this app. 
    <ul>
      <li><p>JSON with Indexed Extractions -- <b>json:google:location:indexedextractions</b></p>
      </li>
      <li><p>JSON with Search Time Extractions -- <b>json:google:location</b></p>
      </li>
    </ul>
  </p>
  <p>
    <br></br><p>
  Both sourcetypes have the same results, however the indexed extractions sourcetype does require some preprocessing before it can be ingested into Splunk properly.
    For this sourcetype, you can trim it up using the following from a gnu linux shell:</p><br></br>
    <font size="4"><pre>$ sed  -i -e '/^{/,+0 d;s/  \"locations\" : \[ {/{/; s/  }, /}\n/;$ d'   LocationHistory.json &amp;&amp;
      sed -i -e '$ s/  } ]/}/' LocationHistory.json</pre></font>
    From here, you can one shot the <b>LocationHistory.json</b> as the <b>json:google:location:indexedextractions</b> sourcetype.
    </p><br></br>
    <b>** Note this based on GNU sed. If you're on OSX or NON-GNU based *Nix, this wont work...</b>  
  <br></br>
  <br></br>
  <br></br>
  <p>See the <b>props.conf</b> in
    <pre>$SPLUNK_HOME/etc/apps/google_timeline/default/props.conf</pre>
  
    </p></font>
  <br></br>
  <p>
    For questions, comments, and requests : <b>ericsix@gmail.com</b>.
  </p>
  </html>
  </panel>

  </row>
</dashboard>